const bodyParts = [
  {
    question: "How many legs do we have?",
    options: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
    correct: "2",
    explanation: "We have two legs to walk and run."
  },
  {
    question: "Which part helps us see?",
    options: ["Ears", "Eyes", "Nose", "Mouth"],
    correct: "Eyes",
    explanation: "We use our eyes to see."
  },
  {
    question: "Which part helps us smell?",
    options: ["Mouth", "Ears", "Nose", "Fingers"],
    correct: "Nose",
    explanation: "Our nose helps us smell things."
  },
  {
    question: "How many arms do we have?",
    options: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
    correct: "2",
    explanation: "We have two arms to lift things and hug."
  },
  {
    question: "Which part helps us hear?",
    options: ["Eyes", "Legs", "Ears", "Hands"],
    correct: "Ears",
    explanation: "Ears help us hear sounds."
  },
  {
    question: "Which part helps us eat?",
    options: ["Hands", "Mouth", "Feet", "Hair"],
    correct: "Mouth",
    explanation: "We eat food using our mouth."
  },
  {
    question: "Which part helps us walk?",
    options: ["Arms", "Eyes", "Legs", "Nose"],
    correct: "Legs",
    explanation: "We use our legs to walk and run."
  },
  {
    question: "What do we use to brush our teeth?",
    options: ["Ears", "Nose", "Hands", "Toes"],
    correct: "Hands",
    explanation: "We hold the brush with our hands."
  },
  {
    question: "Which body part do we wash after playing?",
    options: ["Books", "Bag", "Body", "Board"],
    correct: "Body",
    explanation: "We must wash our body after playing to stay clean."
  },
  {
    question: "Which part of the body do we use to write?",
    options: ["Legs", "Nose", "Hands", "Eyes"],
    correct: "Hands",
    explanation: "We use our hands to hold pencils and write."
  }
];

export default bodyParts;
